
%DisplayName%
%JobTitle% 
P %TelephoneNumber%
F 419-903-0110
%Mail%

%Department%

The information contained in or attached to this communication might be privileged and/or confidential. If you are not the intended recipient of this communication, then please do not use or copy or share with anyone any of the information contained in or attached to this communication. Please be advised that the sender is not granting you any license or permission to use or copy or share any information sent to you in error. If you use or copy or share any information contained in or attached to this email and you are not the intended recipient, then you take such action at your own legal risk and consequence. If you were sent this communication by mistake, then please reply to this message (email/phone) so as to inform the sender of the error and then permanently delete this message and its attachments. Thank you.



